let savollar20 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "beneath",
      answer: "C. ostida",
      options: [
        "A. ustida",
        "B. yonida",
        "C. ostida",
        "D. orqasida"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "cub",
      answer: "A. hayvon bolasi",
      options: [
        "A. hayvon bolasi",
        "B. qush",
        "C. hasharot",
        "D. baliq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "dawn",
      answer: "D. tong",
      options: [
        "A. peshin",
        "B. kech",
        "C. tun",
        "D. tong"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "dissatisfied",
      answer: "B. qoniqmagan",
      options: [
        "A. xursand",
        "B. qoniqmagan",
        "C. zavqlangan",
        "D. minnatdor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "ease",
      answer: "C. osonlik",
      options: [
        "A. qiyinchilik",
        "B. kuch",
        "C. osonlik",
        "D. tezlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "evident",
      answer: "A. ayon",
      options: [
        "A. ayon",
        "B. yashirin",
        "C. murakkab",
        "D. sirli"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "hail",
      answer: "D. do'l",
      options: [
        "A. yomg'ir",
        "B. qor",
        "C. tuman",
        "D. do'l"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to howl",
      answer: "B. uvillamoq",
      options: [
        "A. hurmoq",
        "B. uvillamoq",
        "C. irrillamoq",
        "D. vishillamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to leap",
      answer: "C. sakrab o'tmoq",
      options: [
        "A. emaklamoq",
        "B. yugurmoq",
        "C. sakrab o'tmoq",
        "D. sudralmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "magnificent",
      answer: "A. hashamatli",
      options: [
        "A. hashamatli",
        "B. xunuk",
        "C. oddiy",
        "D. zerikarli"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "necessity",
      answer: "D. zarurat",
      options: [
        "A. hashamat",
        "B. istak",
        "C. tanlov",
        "D. zarurat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "outcome",
      answer: "B. natija",
      options: [
        "A. boshi",
        "B. natija",
        "C. jarayon",
        "D. usul"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "pile",
      answer: "C. uyum",
      options: [
        "A. qator",
        "B. aylana",
        "C. uyum",
        "D. ustun"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "profound",
      answer: "A. chuqur",
      options: [
        "A. chuqur",
        "B. yuzaki",
        "C. oddiy",
        "D. ahamiyatsiz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to seize",
      answer: "D. tutmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qo'yib yubormoq",
        "B. tegmoq",
        "C. silmoq",
        "D. tutmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to squeeze",
      answer: "B. siqmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tortmoq",
        "B. siqmoq",
        "C. ishqalamoq",
        "D. taqillatmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "supreme",
      answer: "C. oliy",
      options: [
        "A. past",
        "B. o'rta",
        "C. oliy",
        "D. oddiy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "terrific",
      answer: "A. ajoyib",
      options: [
        "A. ajoyib",
        "B. dahshatli",
        "C. oddiy",
        "D. o'rtacha"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "trait",
      answer: "D. xususiyat",
      options: [
        "A. ko'rinish",
        "B. qobiliyat",
        "C. mashg'ulot",
        "D. xususiyat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "vital",
      answer: "B. muhim",
      options: [
        "A. zarur emas",
        "B. muhim",
        "C. ixtiyoriy",
        "D. qo'shimcha"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar20;